ILR School Associate Dean's Office Files /4217
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Associate Dean's Office Files
1962-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gray, Lois S. (Lois Spier), 1923-2018
/4217
18.5 cubic feet
18.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8051508
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Ethan Fogg/Casey Westerman, January 16, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4068: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4026: ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity /4296: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals /4296 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Audio-Visual Materials
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Associate Dean's Office; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8051508
- Advisory Committee on Labor Education -- Womens Programs, 1962-1976. (Box 1)
  - Advisory committee on labor education, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Charge policy for union programs, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Decentralization, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Endwell Boces Project, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Extension committee, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Extension evaluation and mission, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Headquarters, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Institute for working men, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Internship Program, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Labor Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo and Rochester Management Studies and Programs, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Legislative support, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Memos from director of extension and to Administration director, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Metro Lease, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan District, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Metro Staff Meetings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Organizational Chart, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Part time extension Teachers, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Personnel information, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Planning Committee Reports, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Private Trade School, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Professorial appapplications of extension staff members, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Proposal Education extension services Personnel, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Staff Meetings, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Publication (proposed) outreach, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Report Card, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sabbatic Leave extension Staff, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Search for director extension, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Extension Staff Report, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Training Specialist Institute, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Two-year labor studies program- Long Island, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Western District, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Wilhelm Weinberg Seminar, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Women's Programs, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Administrative Director Position -- Capital District Labor-Management Programs, 1977-1987. (Box 2)
  - Administrative Director Position, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action Programs, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alcoholism Projects, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Association, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Department of economic research, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Apprenticeship, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Training work experience of apprentices in New York State, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - A core curriculum of related instructions for apprentices, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Work life, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Swanson, etal- The role of related apprenticeship Training, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Devel Program, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Audio Cassette Self Study (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Audio Visual, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Branch Campus Issue, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Budget, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Business Extension Program, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Capital District, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Capital District budget, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Capital District Director Search, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Capital District director search, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Capital District labor programs, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Capital district labor management programs, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Capital District Management Programs -- Extension Booklet, 1977-1987. (Box 3)
  - Capital district Management Programs, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Capital district Programs, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Capital district public sector, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Capital District Public Workshop, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Search Committee Albany Labor Specialist, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Capital Women's Programs, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Career Devel for Mature women, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Combined Albany Office, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Proposal, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Case Statement, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Central Management programs, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Central District labor management programs, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Central District director search, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chancing Law of fair representation, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chase Management Project, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chemical Hazard Information Program, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Curriculum, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Community and economic development institute, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Community Dispute Project, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Con ED Project, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Conference Center, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Conference center planning, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Construction labor relations Cooperative Extension ILR Cooperation, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence A-F, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - G-L, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - M-R, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - S-Z, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Cost Center Budgeting, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Costing Out the Agreement in public school administration, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Credit and Certificate Program, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - District Director's Meetings, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Duty of fair representation, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Economic Dislocation Proposals (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Educational Brokerage Project, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Elderhostel Program, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Empire State College, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Employee Assistant Program, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Employee ownership, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Employment and Workplace Systems, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Executive staff, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Ex-Offenders Program, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Extension Booklet, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Extension Development -- Kellogg Proposal, 1977-1987. (Box 4)
  - Extension Department, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Extension Development Projects, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Extension Director Search, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Extension Directory, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Extension Research, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Funding, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Gifts, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Csea Grievance, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Guidance counselor Seminars, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Guidance counselor workshops on apprenticeship Training, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Harkness Fellowship, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Health project 1 of 3, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Health Project 2 of 3, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Health Project 3 of 3, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hispanic Project 1 of 3, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hispanic Project 2 of 3, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hispanic Project 3 of 3, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Human Service Administration 1 of 3, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Human Service Administration 2 of 3, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Human Service Administration 3 of 3, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Hudson Valley Labor studies, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Industrial Extension, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Innovative Programs, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Institute of Industrial studies, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Instructors, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Inquiries an replies, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Institute for collective bargaining, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Internal Controls, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - International Programs, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - International teams, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Inter District Cooperation, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - IPA Proposal, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Jamestown, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Extension for Job Descriptions, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Kellogg Proposal, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Labor Education Job Application -- MAHWAH, 1977-1987. (Box 5)
  - Labor Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Labor Education Job Application, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Labor Education Position Openings, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Labor Education Proposal, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Labor History Material, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Labor History Project, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Labor Institute For Human Enrichment, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Labor International Exchange, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Search Committee DIR Labor Liberal Arts, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Labor Management 1 of 2, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Labor Management 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Labor Management Committee, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Labor Management Committee Chemung County, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Labor Management Conference, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Labor Program Coordinators, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Labor relations Courses, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Labor Studies on campus Program, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Labor 2000, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - L:abor studies professor search, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Search associate director labor program, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Search- labor studies coordinator, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Labor studies statewide, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Labor Studies teachers, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Labor Studies Tuition rates, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Seminar, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Sanford vs Lenz library, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Local government director search, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Local government programs 1 of 3, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Local government programs 2 of 3, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Local government programs 3 of 3, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Local Government Program -- Memos, 1977-1987. (Box 6)
  - Local Government Program, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Long Island office, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lunches, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mahwah experimental job search, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mailing Lists, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Management Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Management conference F. Plasha, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Management Intern, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Management Job Applicants, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Management Programs Search for Assistant Director, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Management Programs, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Management Studies, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Management Training Materials, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Managerial skills for food Industry District Managers, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cornell pace consortium man power studies program 1 out of 3, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cornell pace consortium man power studies program 2 out of 3, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cornell pace consortium man power studies program 3 out of 3, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Manpower Projects, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Manpower Grant, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Mass transit Project, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Master Degree Program New York City, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Memos, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Burton, John, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Memos to and From George Calvert, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Calvert, George, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Dean, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Moore, Alice, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - W. Whyte, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Labor Program Coordinators, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Memos to extension division staff, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Memos, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Mental Hygiene Project -- On-Campus Labor Summer School, 1977-1987. (Box 7)
  - Mental Hygiene Project N.Y.S Department, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Metro District, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan District Director Search, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Metro Labor Liberal arts program, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Management Programs, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Minority Labor Arbitrator development project, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Metro Programs for new York city government, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Muskiwinni, Joint Foundation Support, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Myers- Briggs type indicator, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Netter Seminar, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - New York Compact, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - New York State Department of labor program, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - OER Management Programs office of employees relations, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - OER- Timely and Effective Griev HAnd1 New York State Donovan Public Service, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - OER Training Program 1 of 3, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - OER Training Program 2 of 3, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - OER Training Program 3 of 3, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Off campus credit courses, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Off campus courses instructors, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - On- Campus Labor Summer School, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- OSHA Oversight Hearings -- OSHA Project, 1977-1987. (Box 8)
  - OSHA Oversight Hearings, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    March 18
  - OSHA: Report on Fourth year grant Activities, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - OSHA 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - OSHA 2 of 2, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - OSHA: Training and education Program, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    May 19
  - OSHA course Manual S. Cupery (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - OSHA project, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - OSHA project 1 of 6, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - OSHA legislation project 2 of 6, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - OSHA project 3 of 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - OSHA project 4 of 6, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - OSHA project 5 of 6, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - OSHA project 6 of 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- OSHA State Project -- PEWS, 1977-1987. (Box 9)
  - OSHA state project, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Outside review, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - PACE Program, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Robert Pasciullo Report, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Peer Tutoring Proposal, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Pending Projects, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - PERB Training R. Helsby1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Personal Actions, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Appointments, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - PEF program, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Policies: Cornell ILR, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Personnel Information A-G, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Personnel Information H-P, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Personnel Information Q-Z, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Programs for employment and workplace systems, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - PEWS, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
- Procedures Puerto Rican Leadership and Training Program, 1977-1987. (Box 10)
  - PEWS 2 of 3, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - PEWS 3 of 3, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Procedures, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Policy Group, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pre-retirement Programs, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Press Relations (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Private Industry Councils, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Program Brochure, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Program Requests, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Public employment programs, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Public Relations, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Public School Organization, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Public Employment Legislative Briefing Session, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Public Sector Training, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Public Service Training Program, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Publication Requests, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Publicity, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Publicity-Buffalo, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Publicity- NYC, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Public- Rochester, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Puerto Rican Leadership Program 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Puerto Rican Leadership Program 2 of 2, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Quality of Work Life -- Western District, 1977-1987. (Box 11)
  - Quality of work life, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Railroad labor relations Project, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Retired Worker Project, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New York State right to know, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Rochester Office, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Labor Management, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Program, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller College of public affairs, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Sex Discrimination in higher education, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Singapore Proposal Ntl Productivity, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Alfred P Sloan Foundation, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Small Business Proposal, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - State Budget, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Rural small business job development program, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Staff Listing organizational chart Flow charts, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Statewide Labor Education Staff, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Statewide Coordination Managemeent Programming, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - statewide summary of programs, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Trade unions women's studies, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Training Series (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Training Coordinators Program (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - TV Proposals, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Union Education Directors (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Union University research conference, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Vaw Seminars, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - UCLEA University and College Labor education association, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Victor Borella center, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Westchester Career Development, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Western District, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Western District 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Western District Management Programs -- Worker Participation Projects, 1977-1987. (Box 12)
  - Western District Management Programs, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Western District Labor Programs, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Working Women's Programs, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Western District Women's Studies, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Women's Caucus, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Womens' Projects, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Women's Project 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Women and Labor Market Conference, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Women and Work institute 1 of 3, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Women and Work institute 2 of 3, 1973-1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Women and Work institute 3 of 3, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Institute for women and work, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Women's Arbitration Project, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Women's Program Metro, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Women's Programs Rochester, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Women's Programs SUNY-ILR, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Women's Projects International, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Training Minority Women for labor EDUCA, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Public Service Women's Studies, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Work Adjustment Project, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Worker Partition Projects, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Labor Studies Files, 1962-1987. (Box 13)
  - Labor Studies-Albany, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Labor Studies Alumni, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Associate Degree Program, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Labor Studies ILR- Brockport, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Labor Studies Buffalo, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Labor Studies Central District, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Enrollment Estimate, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - EEO Studies Program, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Labor Studies Eval, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - General labor studies 1 of 4, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - General labor studies 2 of 4, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - General labor studies 3 of 4, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - General labor studies 4 of 4, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Labor Liberal Arts, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Long Island, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Labor and Management Studies, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Syracuse Labor Studies, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Trade Unions Women's Studies, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - UTICA-Rome Labor Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - VA Benefits, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Written Communications Project-Labor Studies, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Labor Studies Files, 1972-1984. (Box 14)
  - Labor Studies Coordinators Meeting, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Trade Union Women's' studies, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Labor studies TV Proposal, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Labor studies Program Rochester, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Labor Studies Southern Tier, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Labor Studies Coordinators Southern Tier, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Saul Wallen Schol, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Labor Studies Newsletter, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Labor Studies Headcount, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Labor Studies Instructor, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Labor Studies Registration, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Labor Studies Material, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Chrono File 1976 November (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Chrono file 1976 December (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - January 1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - February 1983 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - March 1983 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - April 1983 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - May 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - June 1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - July 1983 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - August 1983 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - September 1983 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - October 1983 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - November 1983 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - December 1983 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - July 1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - August 1984 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - September 1984 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - October 1984 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - November 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - December 1984 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Northeastern Regional Summer Institute for union women, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Leadership workshop photos orders, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - UCLEA SS Information, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Information to be reproduced, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Modes of travel Information, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - NCU Room and workshop information, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Summer Institute, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Northeastern State school, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - 1979 UCLEA Registration Form (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Misc Cornell Information, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - 1979 UCLEA Administration Information and Budget, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - AFL-CIO Convestion, 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - 50th Anniversary NLBR, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Pierce Memorial Conference, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Annual Reports and Summaries of Progress, 1946-1960. (Box 15)
  - Report of the dean, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    New York State school ILR
  - Deans Report to president, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Dean, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Dean, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Deans Report, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Report of the Dean, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    New York State School ILR